{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Dryer Service Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/62020/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62020,"taskName":"Dryer Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair a Dryer","xmTaskDescriptor":"Dryer Service Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":141,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"dryer, clothes dryer, drier, electric dryer, gas dryer","textMessagingName":"Dryer","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes either electric and gas dryers. Dryers must have a vent.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes electric and gas dryers","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Install a Dryer.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Dryer Repair or Install \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Electric \u0026 Gas Dryer Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":3,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Dryer Repair or Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Dryer - Repair or Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Dryer Project","urlName":"Clothes-Dryer-Repair-or-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Clothes Dryer Repair \u0026 Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"dryer, gas, electric, laundry, drier, hook up, hookup, tumble,","emcCategoryOid":-12003,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8422,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62020/":{"taskOID":62020,"originalTaskOID":62020,"setID":8422,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":502645,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of dryer is it?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":" What kind of dryer is it?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of dryer is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gas","answerDisplayText":"Gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500020,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"Type of Service","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203564,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Install a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Repair a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502646,"questionDisplayText":"For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":" For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","shortQuestionText":"For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203508,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203566,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not hot enough","answerDisplayText":"Not hot enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stops turning during the cycle","answerDisplayText":"Stops turning during the cycle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203527,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Too noisy","answerDisplayText":"Too noisy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":502645,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of dryer is it?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":" What kind of dryer is it?","shortQuestionText":"What kind of dryer is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gas","answerDisplayText":"Gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2152,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Electric","answerDisplayText":"Electric","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2738,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Gas","answerDisplayText":"Gas","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500020,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"Type of Service","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203564,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Install a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Repair a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203564,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Install a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203565,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a dryer","answerDisplayText":"Repair a dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502646,"questionDisplayText":"For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":" For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","shortQuestionText":"For installs, have you already purchased the dryer?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203508,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203566,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not hot enough","answerDisplayText":"Not hot enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stops turning during the cycle","answerDisplayText":"Stops turning during the cycle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203527,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Too noisy","answerDisplayText":"Too noisy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203508,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203566,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Not hot enough","answerDisplayText":"Not hot enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203567,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stops turning during the cycle","answerDisplayText":"Stops turning during the cycle","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203527,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Too noisy","answerDisplayText":"Too noisy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}